Guide to the Horace Walpole Collection
The Lewis Walpole Library
- Manuscripts transcribed or annotated by Horace Walpole, Series III
  - [Letter] 1735 Jun 7, from Robert Walpole to Charles, 2d Duke of Richmond / R. Walpole., [2] leaves; 23 cm. (Box 43, Folder 49)
    Annotated by Horace Walpole with a long note about Sir Thomas Prendergast.
  - Epitaph on his wife / [by Sir Edward Walpole; copied by Sir Robert Walpole]., Circa 1739; [1] leaf; 21 cm. (Box 43, Folder 50)
    Endorsed by Horace Walpole: S[i]r Edw[ard] Walpole's epitaph on his wife, Latinized by Dr. Bland, copied out by S[i]r Rob[ert] Walpole.
    First line: She lives, reigns, triumphs in a state of bliss.
  - [Letter] 1749 Nov 6, from Sir Edward Walpole to Mrs. Scott / [copied and annotated by Horace Walpole]., [3] p. on [2] leaves; 20 cm (Box 43, Folder 51)
    Yale Edition, v. 10, Appendix 3, p. 329-31.
  - Epigram made by His Royal Highness William Henry Duke of Gloucester / [copy in the hand of Horace Walpole]. *, 1780; [1] p.; 20 cm. (Box 43, Folder 52)
  - On the death of Lord Harcourt's gardiner 1784 / by Mr. W. Whitehead, [4] p.; 23 cm. (Box 43, Folder 53)
    Title and author from note in Horace Walpole's hand.
    Purchased at: Bonhams' sale of The Roy Davids Collection, part III, 8 May 2013.